Green, Alice P.; Papers apap136
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Campaign Materials, 1998-1999; 5; 0.27 cubic ft.
  - Green Party Platform and Papers, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 2)
  - Strategies, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 3)
  - Media Releases, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 4)
  - Campaign Speeches and Notes, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 5)
  - Publicity Materials, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 6)
  - Friends of Alice Green, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 7)
  - State Board of Elections Papers, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 8)
  - Scripts, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 9)
  - Schedules, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 10)
  - News Clippings, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 11)
  - Voters Guides, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 12)
  - Opponents, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 13)
  - Election Results, 1998 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 14)
  - Green Party Newsletters, 1998, 1999 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 15)
  - Green Party Message Board Postings and E-Mail, 1998, 1999 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 16)
  - Post-Election Publicity, 1998-1999 (Box 6 (5-Campaign Materials), Folder 17)
  - Voter's Guide, Green Party Newsletters, Vote Canvassing Papers, Campaign Buttons, Key Chain, 1998 (Oversized 1)
- Personal Ephemera, ca. 1960-2000; 6; 0.11 cubic ft.
  This series consists of various papers ranging from a few items concerning Alice Green's role in the NAACP's Albany branch and as founder and Executive Director for the Center of Law and Justice, but the majority of the series is relating to her life with her family, including a collection of mentions of her son John A. Green's accomplishments. Highlights of this series include a photograph of Alice Green from the 1960s, race results and other items relating to her running hobby, and Johnnie Cochran's autograph on a menu from a dinner of the One Hundred Black Men of Albany, New York.
  - Business Cards and Resume, ca. 1985 (Box 6 (6-Personal Ephemera), Folder 18)
  - Center for Law and Justice, ca. 1991 (Box 6 (6-Personal Ephemera), Folder 19)
  - NAACP, 1986-1987 (Box 6 (6-Personal Ephemera), Folder 20)
  - Family Items, 1984, 1985; 1987; 1993; 1998; 2000; Undated (Box 6 (6-Personal Ephemera), Folder 21)
  - Alice Green, Photograph, ca. 1960 (Box 6 (6-Personal Ephemera), Folder 22)
  - Johnnie Cochran, Autograph, 1998 (Box 6 (6-Personal Ephemera), Folder 23)
  - Racing Items, 1981; 1988; 1995-2000 (Box 6 (6-Personal Ephemera), Folder 24)